http://www.ceramicmosaicart.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Ceramic Mosaic Art maintains this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. As part of our normal operations, we collect information about you. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
CMA reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. You agree that any changes will be effective when posted on-line at this location and that your continued use of CMA's Services will constitute your acceptance of any changes or additions to this Privacy Policy. You may identify whether CMA has revised this Privacy Policy by noting the Effective Date below.
Information Gathered: When you order from us, you are required to provide certain personal information to us to allow us to process your order. The information you provide to us and that we maintain in our customer account records ranges from basic contact information, to credit card and other payment information. You must provide all of the information we request from you.
Disclosure of Your Information: We will not use your information for internal secondary uses (i.e., uses that do not directly relate to your ordering), or share your information with any third parties for any purpose other than your ordering. We will never willfully sell, lease, or rent any personally identifiable information about you or your business to any third party without first receiving your permission.
We cannot ensure that all of your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be required to disclose personally identifiable information to the government or by court order under certain circumstances. In addition, you authorize us to disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole and exclusive discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.
Security: In order to maximize protection of your information, we use state-of-the-art technology to protect your data from improper use or disclosure, unauthorized access, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all of your personal information, including your credit card number, name, and address, as it is transmitted over the Internet. Of course, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure, and we do not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data on or through the use of our Services is at your own risk. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other sites. All of our employees and contractors who have access to, and are associated with the processing of your information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your personal data.
Corrections and Changes: You have the ability to correct or change certain information in our records, such as your address and contact information. You may change this information at any time and as often as necessary. If you need assistance or have questions about correcting information, you may contact us via email ceramicmosaicartllc@gmail.com. The process for changing your information is described on our website at www.ceramicmosaicart.com.
General: This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Sale that you accept when ordering. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy or our privacy protection practices, please contact Customer Service at ceramicmosaicartllc@gmail.com.
Effective Date: This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 1, 2018.
